https://www.childabuselawyers.com/privacy-policy

Log in
020 8390 4701 - 10:00-13:00 & 14:00-16:00 Tuesday and Thursday only
Welcome /
This page explains how the ACAL (Association of Child Abuse Lawyers) uses any information you give to us, and the way we protect your privacy. Protecting the privacy and personal data of the visitors to our site is of the utmost importance to us.
Accessibility
This site is built with published web standards and accessibility standards in mind, so that it is equally accessible to visitors whatever their abilities or choice of device to access the web. The website aims towards WAI AA accessibility, though recognises that due to user generated content this may not always be possible. If, for any reason, you struggle to view or interact with this site please let us know.
The Data Protection Act
In accordance with the Data Protection Act, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We will only use your information for the purpose as described and we do not pass on your details to any third party unless you have given us permission to do so. You have a right to access your personal data and rectify any inaccuracies.
Site usage
We do not use cookies for collecting user information. Log files allow us to record visitor’s use of the site to enable us to enhance the future layout of the site. The data we gather in this way does not contain any personal information or information about which other sites you have visited.
If you provide feedback on our website we will only use it to develop and improve the site.
Statement coverage
This privacy statement only covers the ACAL (Association of Child Abuse Lawyers) website . It does not cover links within this site to other websites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss and alteration of information under our control.
Changes to the policy
If the privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing the page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, you can contact us through the link below.
Glossary of terms
Cookies are files containing information about visitors to a web site (e.g. user name and preferences). This information is provided by the user during the first visit to a web server. The server records this information in a text file and stores this file on the visitor's hard drive. When the visitor accesses the same web site again the server looks for the cookie and configures itself based on the information provided.
Log files are files created by a web or proxy server which contains all of the access information regarding the activity on that server.
Recent News
November 2020 Newsletter
December 2, 2020 at 1:24 pm
The Anglican Church – Safeguarding in the Church of England and the Church in Wales – Investigation Report
We use cookies to give you the best online experience. By agreeing you accept the use of cookies in accordance with our cookie policy.
I accept
I decline
